How did you sleep?
Well.
Apparently, we’re
getting new neighbours soon, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
When’s your train going?
As usual?
Yes.
At 10.
As every monday.
.
I had a dream.
Want to hear it?
With friends I entered an old warehouse.
White lamps illuminated
a room of white tiles and walls
which yet were dirty.
There also stood a shelf
with things on it
which I did not understand.
We attempted to have ourselves frozen
to get unfrozen again in the future.
Having arrived I learned…
Having arrived I learned
that we were not to choose
when precisely.
Not even getting unfrozen together
was ours to decide.
I had it done anyways.
After all, it was already paid for.
.
And how are you?
So-so.
I’m almost done with preparation.
But it's not that important.
I’m starting to get a bit nervous.
But I’m also happy
because the day is coming closer.
And now,
with all the others
supposedly coming to us...
I mean I always wanted to see New Zealand.
And I’m also coming back, I guess.
Before I forget:
When my brother was here
he gave me a card.
You can keep it if you want.
Think of me when looking at it.
Before I leave
we will definitely do something together.
I promise.
.
What's new?
Some of them have bitten my mother.
It was quite horrible.
My father and I cried.
It all went very fast,
I mean:
her transformation.
At first her wound
swelled red and mother stopped speaking.
Her gums turned black
and she stopped washing herself.
After a while she sat down
on the chair and stopped moving.
The neighbours already started gossiping,
why one did not see her anymore
and why the shutters
on our living room were always let down.
When a neighbour’s boy
tried to press the shutters upwards
we had to move her into the cellar.
At that time her body
was already covered with ulcerous bumps.
.
That is that.
Whenever I could,
I went my way.
It led from my desk
through the village,
on convoluted paths
and far meadows
on to a hidden place.
Every evening this travel was possible
turned the day into a successful one.
I knew that no one
would cross my paths there
and that I could feel at home.
Alone I was,
gazing in amazement
at the magnitude of the setting sun –
yet feeling in company
with the greatest men in history.
Nothing could be compared to this feeling,
to enter an alliance with these very few
in the encounter
with the visage of the sun.
.
Give it to me!
Have you heard about the new ones?
Which new ones?
Now some are
supposed to be also coming here, to us.
Oh, ok.
The clock has stopped.
Oh, I will make it run again then.
How much did that cost?
50.
.
What do you expect from life?
Nothing,I’ll let myself get surprised.
For now I’ll expect something to eat.
…modern technologies
and insights with them into the new world.
But it were
the Chinese who built the railways
and so robbed
the Indians of their spiritual lifestyle…
Do you need much longer?
…in unity with nature…
Turn off the sound!
…nowadays they live in reservations,
in bars and in front of casinos.
Look at what your girlfriend sent to me.
Yeah, she turned really strange.
Turn off the lights, you're luring the gnats!
Turn off the lights,
you're luring the gnats!
Although we are becoming older than ever, our time becomes ever shorter.
Although we are becoming older than ever,
our time becomes ever shorter.
Although the world seems ever smaller,
it becomes ever more confusing.
Although we are gaining ever more insights
…the unknown threatens ever
more pervasively.
- Did you mow the lawn?
What can one do about that?
- Yes.
We have asked professor doctor Kruse.
- Did you have a good time
with your friends?
In spite of all dangers there is
no reason to be afraid.
- Yes.
…by taking preventive measures.
- When's your train going?
Going to bed early,...
…a balanced diet and thinking positively
do wonders there.
- At 10...
...as every Tuesday.
Yoga and meditation are also recommended.
Which of the diverse options one finally
uses is a matter of taste, naturally.
- Do you need any money?
Where do you want to
be when the end is nigh?
be when the other is nigh?
Depression or inner peace?
The choice is yours.
Ah.
It's you.